[{"answer": "What's wrong", "docId": "Tall-in-the-Saddle.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " What's wrong with law and order", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Afternoon ma'am. my friend ain't it", "docId": "Tall-in-the-Saddle.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " Glad to know you, miss", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I tell ya I ain't never had any hide", "docId": "Tall-in-the-Saddle.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " Yes", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " When anybody plays poker with me, they play my game or not at all", "docId": "Tall-in-the-Saddle.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " Comes back", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " How do you do, ladies", "docId": "Tall-in-the-Saddle.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " Yes", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " That does it, boys", "docId": "Tall-in-the-Saddle.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Not until I get my money", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " Say, Arly", "docId": "Tall-in-the-Saddle.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " Forget it", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Well", "docId": "Tall-in-the-Saddle.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " Make love to you", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " Make love to you", "docId": "Tall-in-the-Saddle.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Did you expect me to deny that, too", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Don't be so sure", "docId": "Tall-in-the-Saddle.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Don't you know", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Don't you know", "docId": "Tall-in-the-Saddle.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " I always get what I want", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " You murderer", "docId": "Tall-in-the-Saddle.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " Then who did", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " You vile, ungrateful strumpet", "docId": "Tall-in-the-Saddle.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " -- And don't think I don't know what you intend doing", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " But what'll we do with the ole lady", "docId": "Tall-in-the-Saddle.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I'd like to pizen her", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "That means you're goin' back East", "docId": "Tall-in-the-Saddle.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "It's good to know where you Belong, I reckon", "qsentId": 30}]